a mess between two old senile people like this,
заварушка двух старых маразматик вот так
or rather, no, not so old, senile
вот точнее нет не так старого маразматик
and
и
a clown, it’s cool, but who attacked whom? an
клоуна прикольно то а кто на кого напал
old senile person attacks a clown, or a clown attacks an
старый маразматик на клоуна или клоун на
old senile person, in general, in theory, an
старого мариз матика вообще по идее
old senile person attacks a clown, otherwise it’s
старый маразматик на клоуна а то это
a mess between an old senile person and
заварушка старого марз матика получается
not an old one  marz matik and clown no the
а не старого марз матика и клоуна нет
clown also took part in this
клоун тоже в этом участие
Hello Hello, you are 18 years old are you
Здравствуйте Вам 18 лет есть есть вы
from
откуда из
Krasnoyarsk I am originally from Rostov But I
Красноярска Я сам родом из Ростова Но
live in California 18 years in 2 years I
живу в Калифорнии 18 лет через 2 года
will be
будет
20 you are talking
двадцатом общаетесь
about what I
О чём
will have to talk about on the go so to speak
придётся ваю на ходу так сказать А вы
What are you  want with
что хотите со
me I don’t know some very serious e and
мной не знаю какой-то очень серьёз е и
Rome
Риме
since I’m just not this previous person I
раз я просто не это предыдущий человек я
told him a little and he
ему немножко говорил а он
switched off I’m a serious person yes I’m
отключился Я в я серьёзный человек да Я
here in the city of Folsom I’m
вот у нас в городе фолсом я это
in Russian a deputy of the city council of the
по-русски депутат городского совета
city
городской
duma  decently Well, this is how it is in Russia, so
думы прилично Ну это в России так
the deputy is still dragging along, but here it’s
депутат все ж прямо тащатся а у нас это
not like everyone is dragging along. And you’re
да нет не то чтобы тащится всем А вам
afraid to talk seriously,
страшно поговорить серьёзны
no, then relax, have
м нет Тода расслабьтесь получайте
fun, Yes, I don’t seem to be tense, so
удовольствие Да я вроде не напряжена так
what do you want me to not ask the
о чём хотите чтобы чтобы я не задавал
topic about?  you want to
тему О чём вы хотите
talk, I don’t even know Well, well, Ask
поговорить даже не знаю Ну ну Задайте
a topic, then I’ll be a man,
тему ла я тогда на правах мужчины буду
but you may not like it, I’ll have
но вам может не понравится я буду
tough topics, how do you feel about the fact that
жёсткие темы как относитесь к тому что
Russia attacked
Россия напала на
Ukraine Absolutely no difference, I have nothing
Украину Абсолютно без разницы Я не имею
to do with this, I just think that
отношения Я просто считаю что
this  a mess between two old senile people like
это заварушка двух старых маразматик вот
this, or rather, no, not so old
так вот точнее нет не так старого
senile and a
маразматик и
clown, it’s cool, who attacked whom? an
клоуна прикольно то а кто на кого напал
old senile person attacks a clown, or a clown attacks an
старый маразматик на клоуна или клоун на
old senile person, in general, in theory, an
старого мариз матика вообще по идее
old senile person attacks a clown, otherwise it
старый маразматик на клоуна а то это
turns out to be a mess between an old martik and a clown. They are
заварушка старого мартика получается Они
old Morse batik  and there is no clown, the clown
старого морз батика и клоуна нет клоун
also took part in this, in
тоже в этом участие принимал это на
fact, both are to blame like this, well, which one is to
деле оба виноваты вот так вот ну какой
blame, someone is more to blame, someone is
вот в чём винова кто-то больше кто-то
less to blame, that’s what Ukraine is to blame for being
меньше вот в чём виновата Украина что на
attacked Explain to me, I’m interested,
неё напали Объясни мне мне интересно
I’m just not quarreling.  I wonder how
просто я не ссорюсь Мне интересно как
the Russians who are neutral, how they
россияне которые нейтральные как они
think Well, it’s just that it wasn’t done from
мыслят Ну просто это же сделано не на
scratch, right. Well, I don’t know
пустом месте правильно Ну я не знаю на
which one. Why they attacked the DPR, but
каком Почему напали именно на ДНР же
no one bombed eight or whatever
никто не бомбил восемь или сколько там
six Russia bombed Russia bombed yes
шесть Россия Бомбила Россия Бомбила да
Russia Bombed their own, what are you doing?  theirs
Россия Бомбила свои же эти Ты что свои
or something So the Donetsk and Lugansk region
что ли Так Донецкая и Луганская область
is
- это
Ukraine, it’s Ukraine that couldn’t bomb
Украина это Украина не могла бомбить
its own, look, come on, the Donetsk and Lugansk
свои смотри давай Донецкая и Луганская
region were all Ukraine Until Russia
область это всё было Украина Пока Россия
recognized them and
не признала их и не
annexed them, since what year is this part of
присоединила с какого года эта часть
Russia considered
России считается
[music]
[музыка]
Now we’ll find out
Сейчас узнаем
Come on, the second one turns out to be dgo, that is, it
Давай д второго получается дго то есть
turns out that it
получается
became officially Russia in 2005. That is, for
стал официально россие в 2 году То есть
8 years it was part of Ukraine, then Ukraine
8 лет это была часть Украины то Украина
means according to your words. Well, it’s not possible for a
значит по твоим словам Ну не можно чтоб
country to Bomb its territory, which means
страна Бомбила свою территорию значит
after all Russia Bombed, I don’t believe the words of
всё-таки Бомбила Россия я верю словам не
people from the Internet, I  I believe the words of the people
людей из интернета я верю словам людям
who lived there, I and the people who
которые там жили я жи люди которые
spoke about
говорили об
it well How long ago have you
этом хорошо Как давно раз Вы уже 18
been in California for 18 years? Yes, and I came as a
лет в Калифорнии ти Жил да а приезжал я
US citizen, but I lived in Donetsk in the
гражданином США но я жил в Донецке в
damn year, I just come once every
чертом году я просто приезжаю раз в
six months to the USA. To be honest  already
полгода в США меня Если честно уже
so E topic with
настолько Э тема с
every that Well, here it sits with
кажд что Ну вот тут вот это сидит ко у
you here it sits, I understand this
тебя вот тут сидит я понимаю это потому
because no one wants to listen to your opinion
что никто не хочет слушать твоего мнения
Everyone thinks that
Каждый думает что прав
he is right Look at this, you think It’s time
он Смотри это думае Поре
Ukraine didn’t Bomb its territory
Украина не Бомбила свою территорию
because it’s Russia’s territory
потому что это е территория Россия
I bombed these 8 years, it turns out that I understand
Бомбила эти 8 лет получается я понимаю
that you want me to name the country in
что ты лю хо чтобы я назвала страну в
which I live, what I
которой я живу
want is to just sort it out, you said that
что хочу просто разобрали ты сказала что
both are to blame, I asked like this: What is
виноваты оба я спросил так А в чём
Ukraine to blame for, that it was attacked by
Украина виновата что на неё напали
Russia, it means Russia is to blame,
Россия напала значит Россия виновата всё
simply, or what?  well, nothing happens
ж просто или как ну ничего не происходит
out of nowhere, I’m not a politician, there’s
на пустом месте я не политик наверно
probably something there, she’s probably to blame, but
есть в чём-то наверное она виновата хо
if you were walking down the street and
если если ты шла по улице и тебе
someone broke your nose, is it
какой-то взял пролома нос что-то в этом
your fault or
ты виновата или
not, it doesn’t just happen that it
нет не бывает же просто так чтобы
breaks  the nose is true
пролома нос правда
You don’t compare such things, why is this a
Ты не сравнивай такие вещи почему это
bad comparison? Because when
плохое сравнение Потому что когда тебе
someone on the street lightens your nose for fun,
на улице кто-то по приколу пролайт нос
it’s [ __ ] trouble for a specific person,
это [__] беды у человека конкретного
one with his head off,
одного с башкой
Tina’s head off falls on another country,
у Тина с башкой опадает на другую страну
that’s the same thing, that’s good Putin, this is what you
вот тоже самое хорошо Путин ты вот это
expect  words look at what Putin I know
ожидаешь слы смотри то что Путин Я знаю
you explain to me What Ukraine is to blame for
ты мне объясни В чём Украина виновата
You’re just saying why I have to
Просто ты говоришь почему я тебе должна
explain this to you Well you said that
это объяснить что ты ж сказала что
Ukraine is also to blame I said that I
Украина тоже виновата я сказала что я в
don’t understand this but I’m more than
этом не разбираюсь но я больше чем
sure that there is something  so why do
уверена что что-то есть есть так с чего
you, why do you have this confidence? Where do
ты с чего эта уверенность Откуда это у
you get this confidence in your head that something
тебя в голове уверенность что что-то
exists, nothing happens just
есть ничего не бывает просто
like that? And what does Ukraine have to do with it? It’s not
так так А причём тут Украина я т не
just that Russia took and attacked
просто так Россия взяла и напала на
Ukraine because it’s because the
Украину потому что она потому что у
old grandfather had  In short, the Kremlin has
старого деда в Кремле в башке короче
jelly in his head, he doesn’t have any potency,
кисель у него не встаёт нету потенции
he needs to realize himself somehow, and
ему надо как-то реализовываться да
what does Ukraine have to do with it
причём Украина
[music]
[музыка]
here now for a second we need to clarify one moment,
тут сейчас секунду надо один момент
just clarify then why Russia attacked
просто тогда почему Россия напала на
Ukraine simply because it Well, what kind of
Украину просто потому что она Ну что это
nonsense is this too? Well, there is  Well, what are some
тоже за бредятина Ну есть же какие-то
reasons? Well, what if any?
причины Ну какие вот если какие-то то
What are the reasons on the part of Russia? When
Какие причины со стороны России при
Russia wants to seize new territories,
Россия хочет захватить новые территории
new people, these New territories e.g. 1
новых люди эти Новые территории е так 1
sushi because yes, they think that it is necessary to
суши потому что да считают что нужно
take away everything that was in the Soviet Union and
забрать всё что было в Советском Союзе и
in the Russian
в Российской
empires whatever they are not Mongols Tatars
империи как их там не монголы татары
Mongols gi
монголы ги
you are like Hitler Hitler also attacked And
вы как Гитлер вот Гитлер тоже напал А
that Hitler attacked the USSR it turns out that the USSR
что Гитлер напал на СССР получается ССР
was also to blame, nothing, it just doesn’t
тоже был виноват ничего ж Просто так не
happen Hitler attacked the USSR because
бывает Гитлер напал на СССР потому что
he was a man who had
он человек у которого был
some Well, this one  nonsense in my head like
какой-то Ну вот этот бред в голове типа
about the fact that one nation is the main one like Putin
про то что одна нация главная как Путин
yes Okay And what this does now is
да Хорошо И что это делает теперь
not a question for Russians When Hitler is just
русских не вопрос Когда Гитлер просто
interested in the same logic when Hitler
интересно в этой же логике когда Гитлер
attacked the USSR it turns out that the USSR was also
напал на СССР получается СССР тоже был
to blame, this is the same topic as breaking
виноват это та же тема что и проломить
your nose, this is trouble  in the head of one specific
нос это беды в башке одного конкретного
person Then the question Yes, I understand why
человека Тогда вопрос Да я понял почему
then when Russia attacks Ukraine, then
тогда когда Россия нападает на Украину
Ukraine is also to blame because it
значит Украина тоже виновата потому что
doesn’t happen that it is not to blame. And
не бывает так чтобы не было виновато А
when Hitler attacks the USSR, Germany
когда Гитлер нападает на СССР Германия
attacked the USSR, then the USSR is not to blame, then
напала на ССР то СССР не виноват то ги
Germany attacked the USSR  Because
Германия напала на СССР Потому что
why Because
почему Потому
we’ll take over the whole world right,
что захватим весь мир правильно
right Well, the USSR was also to
правильно Ну СССР тоже было
blame, now you’re going to spread rot on me for this
виновата ты меня теперь за это гнобить
again, you’ll just give it
будешь ещё раз это Приведёшь просто вот
as evidence of yours, well,
как доказательства сво ну
really, you gave an example. Why,
реально ты привела пример Да что у
Ukraine is also to blame because it doesn’t
Украина тоже виновата потому что не
happen just like that  I say then it
бывает так что просто так Я говорю тогда
turns out that Germany attacked the USSR,
получается что Германия напала на СССР
too, the USSR is to blame. Because it doesn’t
тоже СССР виноват Потому что не бывает
just happen that the same logs in
просто так то же самой логи в
California, such logic turns out that the USSR is to
Калифорнии такая логика получается ССР
blame, too, that Hitler cash Yes, there
виноват тоже что Гитлер нал Да всё
is no logic,
логики нету
I
я
agree
согласен
Well, I agree with its conclusions, put a
Ну я согласен с е выводами поставьте
plus sign to I agree and  like pips comment
плюсик ко согласен и лайк пипс комент
how they are In short, they are tearing up Yes, Ukraine is also
как они Короче э их рвёт Да Украина тоже
to blame What Well, it doesn’t happen that it’s not
виновата В чём Ну не бывает же чтобы не
to blame anyway, like their theme
виновато всё равно там как ихняя тема
balalaika, there are always two to blame Yes, anyway,
балалайка виноваты же всегда двое Да всё
there’s no smoke without fire But
равно что-то нет дыма без огня А ведь
somewhere somewhere-  then somehow something about something
что-то где-то как-то что-то о чём-то
too yes yes but when you give them
тоже да да но когда им приводишь
similar examples if you get your
аналогичный примеры если тебе разбивают
nose broken on the street just because it’s your fault
нос на улице просто так ты в чём виноват
and not this other thing And when Germany attacked the
а не это другое А когда Германия напала
Soviet Union and not this other thing So
на Советский Союз а не это другое Так
why when  Putin attacks Ukraine
почему когда Путин нападает на Украину
is one thing, but Hitler attacks the USSR - that’s
это одно а Гитлер нападает на ССР - это
another, the
другое тоже
same thing in my head Yes, it’s the same thing that
самое в голове Да вот тоже самое что у
Putin has in his head, it’s just one to one
Путина в голове вот просто один в один
what kind of training manuals they have Yes, they
какие методички у них Да в головах
just sit in their heads like pska
просто сидят лайк пска
comment Write on th instag I don’t  I know
комент Пиши на й instag Я не знаю для
why is this for Why are you there to marvel at
чого це тоб Для чего тоб там дивитись
otsem miy face Ale for you tse one two
оце мий фейс Але для тебе це один два
or three clicks Ale you trime me and I
або три клика Але ты тримае мене и я
will say Wow in me there is a Kupa of fouls and
буду казати Вау в мене там Купа фолов и
in me there will be a classy mood to robiti
в мене буде класний настрий щоб робити
but cool video write on th  Instagram Popik
но крут вдео пись на й Instagram Попик
Andriy
Андрий вот
like this, let me check for you
так давай я тебя